Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Toscanini recordings
  - Trumpet Prelude - Purcell, arr. Stokowski, hupka_3633; D6-RC-5612-2; 11-9419A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Trumpet Prelude - Purcell; Pavane - ?, hupka_1876; 066728-2A; Shellac disc
  - Trumpet Tune and Air - Purcell, hupka_1909; 071212-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Turandot - Nessun dorma - Puccini, hupka_0826; OSB-2399-2; 10-1200-B; Shellac disc
  - Turandot - Nessun dorma - Puccini, hupka_0838; OSB-2399-2; 10-1200-B; Shellac disc
  - Twelve Songs, op. 21 - Lilacs - Rachmaninoff, hupka_2151; 072132-1; Shellac disc
  - Two Grenadiers - Schumann, hupka_1253; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Two Grenadiers [Les deux grenadiers] - Robert Schumann, 3/14/1906; hupka_4120; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Two Grenadiers [Les deux grenadiers] - Robert Schumann, 3/14/1906; hupka_4121; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Two Sonatas in A Major - Domenico Scarlatti, hupka_1295; 072595-2; Shellac disc
  - Un ange est venu - Henri Bemberg, 3/26/1907; hupka_0902; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un ange est venu - Henri Bemberg, hupka_0903; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Alla vita - Verdi, 1907; hupka_1103; Serial # 877-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Alla vita - Verdi, 1907; hupka_1104; Serial # 877-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un ballo in maschera - Alla vita che t'arride - Verdi, [3/2/1905]; hupka_3281; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un ballo in Maschera - Di' tu se fedele - Verdi, 10/28/1907; hupka_1680; Serial # B-4899; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Di tu se fedele - Verdi, 1930; hupka_3778; 7236-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un ballo in maschera - Eri tu - Verdi, [02/10/1905]; hupka_4072; Serial # 85044; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Eri tu - Verdi, 4/3/1907; hupka_1091; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Eri tu - Verdi, hupka_1111; Serial # 92044; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Eri tu - Verdi, hupka_1112; Serial # 886-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Eri tu - Verdi, [04/21]1905; hupka_1975; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Eri tu - Verdi, [09/18]/1903; hupka_1983; IRCC-86-A; Shellac disc
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - M'ami, m'ami - Verdi, circa 1906-1917; hupka_1951; 3204-C; 054071; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Ma dall'arido - Verdi, circa 1930-1939; hupka_3921; 6770-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Ma dall'arido stelo divulca - Verdi, 1906; hupka_1950; 92000; 6414-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Ma se m'e forza perderti - Verdi, 12/27/1911; hupka_3667; A-11420; Shellac disc
  - Un ballo in Maschera - Morrò, ma prima in grazi - Verdi, hupka_0991; Serial # A-24927; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Morte di Riccardo - Finale - Verdi, 1930; hupka_3779; 7236-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Saper vorreste - Verdi, hupka_1896; 570-M; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Saper vorreste - Verdi, circa 1903-1915; hupka_3936; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Un Ballo in Maschera - Volta la terra - Verdi, 6/9/1915; hupka_3554; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Uocchie di suonno - Pasquale Mario Costa, 11/23/1911; hupka_2862; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Valse - Luigi Arditi, hupka_1906; 576-M; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme by Haydn, op. 56a - Brahms (conc.), 2/20/1948; hupka_2192; Dress rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme by Haydn, op. 56a - Var. I - Brahms, 2/20/1948; hupka_2186; Dress rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme by Haydn, op. 56a - Var. II, III, IV - Brahms, 2/20/1948; hupka_2187; Dress rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme by Haydn, op. 56a - Var. V, VI, VII - Brahms, 2/20/1948; hupka_2188; Dress rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme by Haydn, op. 56a - Var. VII, VIII - Brahms, 2/20/1948; hupka_2191; Dress rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme from The Magic Flute - Mozart/Beethoven, hupka_3279; Disc 1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme from The Magic Flute - Mozart/Beethoven, hupka_3285; Disc 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme from The Magic Flute - Mozart/Beethoven, hupka_3287; Disc 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Variations on a Theme from The Magic Flute - Mozart/Beethoven, hupka_3289; Disc 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Verdi, Mozart], 12/31/1903 ]; hupka_4074; Serial # 85016; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1 - Don Giovanni - Serenata [Deh vieni alla finestra] - Mozart Side 2 - Falstaff - Quand'ero paggio del Duce di Norfolk - Verdi
  - [Verdi, Mozart], [10/06/1909]; hupka_4075; Serial # 3743-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [Verdi, Mozart], [10/06/1909]; hupka_4076; Serial # 3743-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
    Side 1 - Don Giovanni, K. 527 - Serenata [Deh vieni alla finestra] - Mozart Side 2 - Falstaff - Quand'ero paggio del Duce di Norfolk - Verdi
  - Veronique - The Swing Song - André Messager [lyricists - Percy Greenbank & Lilian Eldée], 11/27/1911; hupka_1012; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Vicar of Bray - ? Watson, 1903; hupka_2886; Serial # 3861-R; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Victor Chorale Show, hupka_3624; T-2734-1A; Shellac disc
  - Victor Chorale Show, hupka_3627; T-2734-1; Shellac disc
  - Victor Chorale Show, hupka_3628; T-2733-1A; Shellac disc
  - Victor Chorale Show, hupka_3629; T-2733-1A; Shellac disc
  - Victor Chorale Show OR Faust - Gounod, hupka_3630; D6-RC-5270-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Violin Concerto - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn (Part 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_3881; Record # D4-RC-139-1A; "NG" = No Good?; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn (Part 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_3895; Record # D4-RC-139-1A;; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto - Mvt. III - Mendelssohn (conclusion), 4/9/1944; hupka_3907; Record # D4-RC-142-1A;; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn (Pt. 1), 4/9/1944; hupka_2221; D4-RC-137; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn (Pt. 1), 4/9/1944; hupka_2233; D4-RC-137; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn (Pt. 2), 4/9/1944; hupka_2222; D4-RC-138; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn (Pt. 2), 4/9/1944; hupka_2234; D4-RC-138; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_2223; D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_2224; D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_2227; D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_2228; D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_2229; D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 3), 4/9/1944; hupka_2235; D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 4), 4/9/1944; hupka_2230; D4-RC-140; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. II - Mendelssohn (Pt. 4), 4/9/1944; hupka_2236; D4-RC-140; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. III- Mendelssohn (Pt. 5), 4/9/1944; hupka_2231; D4-RC-141; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. III- Mendelssohn (Pt. 5), 4/9/1944; hupka_2241; D4-RC-141; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. III- Mendelssohn (Pt. 6), 4/9/1944; hupka_2232; D4-RC-142; Shellac disc
  - Violin Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. III- Mendelssohn (Pt. 6), 4/9/1944; hupka_2242; D4-RC-142; Shellac disc
  - Voce di Primavera - Johann Strauss II [arr. Frank LaForge], [11/05/1904]; hupka_4057; Serial # 85036; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Voices of Christmas, 12/25/1957; hupka_2286; Sides 2 & 4; 3803; VinylDisc
  - Voices of Christmas, 12/25/1957; hupka_2289; Sides 1 & 3; 3803; VinylDisc
  - Voices of Christmas, Sides 1 & 3, 12/7/1955; hupka_2280; 506-212; VinylDisc
  - Voices of Christmas, Sides 1 & 3, 12/7/1955; hupka_2281; 506-212; VinylDisc
  - Voices of the Spring - Johann Strauss II, hupka_0813; Shellac disc
  - [Weber, Bizet, Donizetti, Verdi, Ponchielli, Thomas], hupka_4150; Sides 3 & 4; E3-RP-5202 & 5203; VinylDisc
    Invitation to the Dance - Weber; Carmen Suite No. 1 - Bizet; Don Pasquale - Overture - Donizetti; La Forza del Destino - Overture - Verdi; La Gioconda - Dance of the Hours - Amilcare Ponchielli; Mignon - Overture - Ambroise Thomas
  - Werther - Ah non mi ridestar - Massenet, hupka_0802; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Werther - Ma come dopo il nembo - Massenet, hupka_3474; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Werther - Why awaken me - Massenet, 1909; hupka_3917; 1980-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Whither, whither have you gone - Tschaikowsky, 1910; hupka_3918; 1986-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Wiegenlied - Mozart, 6/8/1915; hupka_3566; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Wiegenlied, D. 498 - Schubert, 1/13/1915; hupka_3896; IRCC-5012-B; 87214; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - William Tell - Overture Part 4 - Rossini, hupka_2178; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - William Tell - Overture Part 4 - Rossini, hupka_2190; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - William Tell - Troucar suoi Ol! - Rossini, circa 1908-1910; hupka_0877; Serial # 1187-C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - William Tell - Two Dances - Rossini, hupka_1653; Serial # D5-RC-495-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - William Tell [Guillame Tell] - Resta immobile e ver la terra - Rossini, May, 1912; hupka_3475; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Within a Mile of Edinboro' Town - James Hook, lyricist - Thomas D'Urfey, 1906; hupka_3863; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Wraith (Der Doppelgänger) - Schubert, hupka_1085; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Xerxes - Largo - Handel, hupka_3429; 3486-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Xerxes [Serse], HWV 40 - Praise ye the Lord - Handel, hupka_3456; OEA-9316-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Zampa - Overture - Ferdinand Hérold (Part 1), 4/4/1943; hupka_1355; No. 95; VinylDisc
  - Zampa - Overture - Ferdinand Hérold (Parts 1 & 2), 4/4/1943; hupka_1308; No. 95; VinylDisc
  - Zampa - Overture - Ferdinand Hérold (Parts 1 & 2), 4/4/1943; hupka_1309; No. 95; VinylDisc
  - Zampa - Perche tremar - Louis Hérold, hupka_3476; 889-C; 052148; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Zampa - Perche tremar - Louis Hérold, hupka_3477; IRCC-202-B; Shellac disc
  - [ILLEGIBLE], hupka_1321; Shellac disc
  - [ILLEGIBLE], hupka_1322; Shellac disc
  - [ILLEGIBLE], hupka_1918; D5-RC-477-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [ILLEGIBLE], hupka_1919; V-301; Shellac disc
  - [ILLEGIBLE] - Luigi Arditi, hupka_1895; 566-M; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [ILLEGIBLE] - Scarlatti, hupka_3641; D6-RC-7967-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_0022; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - [unknown], hupka_0559; Bach or Schubert?; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - [unknown], hupka_0611; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - [unknown], hupka_0612; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - [unknown], hupka_1160; CK-1254-1; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1161; CK-1254-1; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1162; CK-1254-1; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1343; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1344; D8-RC-1-1A; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1345; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1369; D6-RC-5612-2; Cat # 11-9419-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1370; D7-RC-7890-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1371; D5-RC-8-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1436; Serial # 91076; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1448; Serial # 87157; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1460; Serial # 1471-B; could possibly be a Victor Mx #; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1472; Serial # BK 1832; not vocal; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1693; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1694; D8-RC-26-1; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1879; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1880; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1881; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_1923; #T-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1924; Test; HB-9-12; Silvered from lacquer - pressed from orig. master; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1925; # 2-3-4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1926; # 4-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1927; # 4-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1928; # 5-6-7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1929; # 7C-8; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1930; # F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1931; # 1-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_1932; Test-B-942; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2020; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2024; D7-RC-8004-1A; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2032; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2037; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2038; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2043; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2045; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2048; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2049; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2050; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2051; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2052; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2053; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2054; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2055; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2056; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2057; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2065; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2068; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2073; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2085; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2086; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2087; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2088; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2089; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2090; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2091; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2092; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2093; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2096; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2097; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2098; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2099; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2100; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2101; D8-RC-1-1R; Test; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2102; Copy; Test; Side 5; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2103; Copy; Test; Side 9; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2104; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2105; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2108; 19; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2110; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2111; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2112; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2116; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2129; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2130; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2131; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2134; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2136; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2140; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2141; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2147; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2149; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2150; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2160; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2161; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2180; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2185; Shellac disc
  - [unknown], hupka_2282; VinylDisc
  - [unknown], hupka_2297; 4 Unknown records in hand-made "album; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2375; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2376; 6A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2377; 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2378; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2379; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 2/15/1947; hupka_2380; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 2/15/1947; hupka_2381; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2382; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2383; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2386; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2387; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2388; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2389; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2398; 066529-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2399; 066529-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/6/1941; hupka_2412; 066534-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2430; MS-45545-1; Part 1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2431; MS-45546-1; Part 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2434; MS-45547-1; Part 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2435; MS-45548-1; Part 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2436; MS-45549-1; Part 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2437; MS-45550-1; Part 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2443; # 043487; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2448; Test; MS-045545-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2449; Test; MS-045546-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2450; Test; MS-045547-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2451; Test; MS-045548-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2452; Test; MS-045549-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2453; Test; MS-045530-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2459; 050411; Test; Speech?; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2460; Speech?; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2461; Test; MS-018216-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2462; Test; MS-018217-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2463; Test; MS-018218-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2464; Test; MS-018219-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2465; Test; MS-018220-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2466; Test; MS-018221-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2467; Test; MS-018222-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2470; Test; MS-018223-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2471; Test; MS-019992-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2472; Test; MS-019993-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2473; Test; MS-019994-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2474; Test; MS-019995-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2475; Test; MS-019996-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2476; Test; MS-019997-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2477; Test; MS-019998-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2478; # 021500-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2479; # 021501-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2484; # 021502-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2486; # 021504-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2487; # 021505-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2488; # 021506-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2489; # 021507-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2490; # 021508-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2500; MS 043426-1; Part 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2501; MS 043427-1; Part 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2503; MS 043488-1; Part 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2504; MS 043489-1; Part 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2505; MS 043490-1; Part 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2508; MS 043490-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2509; MS 043491-1; Part 5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2510; MS 043491-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2511; MS 043492-1; Part 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2512; MS 043492-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2513; MS 043493-1; Part 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2514; MS 043493-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2515; MS 043494-1; Part 8; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2517; MS 045517-1; Part 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 11/25/1939; hupka_2521; MS 045518-1; Part 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2540; Record # ND5-MM-5235; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2542; Record # ND5-MM-5236; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2545; Record # ND5-MM-5237; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2546; Record # ND5-MM-5238; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2547; Record # ND5-MM-5239; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2548; Record # ND5-MM-5240; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2549; Record # ND5-MM-5241; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2550; Record # ND5-MM-5242; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2609; #1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2610; #2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2611; #3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2612; #4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2613; #5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/10/1947; hupka_2614; #6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2615; #11; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2616; #12; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2619; #10; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2620; #9; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2621; #8; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2622; #7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2623; #6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2624; #5; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2625; #4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2626; #3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2627; #2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2628; #1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2631; #8; 8C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2632; #7; 7C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2633; #6; 6C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2634; #1; 1C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2635; #5; 5C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2636; #4; 4C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2637; #3; 3C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 1/13/1945; hupka_2638; #2; 2C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2741; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2742; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2743; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 3/15/1947; hupka_2806; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2846; ND3-MM-3203-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2851; ND3-MM-3204; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2852; ND3-MM-3205-2B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2853; ND3-MM-3206-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2854; ND3-MM-3203-4B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2896; Part 6; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2899; Parts 5 & 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2911; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2912; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2919; ND6-MM-4017 & 4019; "Sibelius 4 mov.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 4/27/1940; hupka_2920; Part 4; 050077-1; Tracks on item come from this broadcast, but do not include all titles listed; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2923; Sibelius 3 mvt.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2924; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2925; Sibelius 1 & 2 mvt.; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2926; 045516-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2927; 037992-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2928; 043428-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2929; MS-043487-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2930; 045521-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], 12/11/1947; hupka_2932; ¼" thick, glass record; Side 9; Afternoon; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2935; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2954; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2980; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2981; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2982; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [unknown], hupka_2985; Lacquer discs/acetates